BARIBOR PAAGO

Software Engineer

S 09035401231

<u>bariborpaago@gmail.com</u>







Junior software engineer, currently serving as an intern front-end developer at Fairexx Solutions, I have previously served as an Data entry personnel and later as front-end intern developer at MeshView Limited. I adopt a SCRUM/AGILE approach to software development and I have been lucky to work with some of the latest technologies in web development, I implemented a front-end development cycle at MeshView that helped speed up software development speed by 30%, at Fairexx I am automating most of the manual tasks and increasing productivity by approx 20%, I have knowledge of multiple high-level programming languages and can work with modern software development tools and frameworks, I am a fast learner

WORK EXPERIENCES

Software Developer Intern

Fairexx Solutions

2021-Present

- Responsible for transforming wireframe designs into codes.
- Build Interactive and responsive user interfaces
- Work in agile and collaborative environment to deliver tasks the meet projects requirement.

Front-end Developer Intern

MeshView Limited

2018-2020

- Implemented front-end technical solutions to meet projects requirement for web pages
- Assist the team in building software products

Data Entry Personnel

MeshView Limited

2018

- Meet up daily target for client sites.
- Pay attention to details while recording data

Software Developer Student

Riv-TechCreek

2018

- Learnt how to build web applications.
- Collaborate with a team to complete a timely projects.

SKILLS

Technical

- HTML5
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- lavaScript
- React.is
- Agile Methodologies

Professional

- Creative
- Team worker
- Reliable
- Ideation

EDUCATION

Electrical/Electronics Engineering Kenule Beeson Polytechnic, Bori 2016 - 2020

PROJECTS

- Portfolio website www.bariborpago.netlify.app
- Pureearth www.pureearth.netlify.app
- MyclothLivery www.myclothlivery.netlify.app